[Music]
You can quickly get your products in front of millions of Japanese customers by selling on Amazon
Japan.
Japan has a population of 128 million people and 70% of them shop online.
Amazon Japan has millions of customers every month.
In this video, we're going to show you the Amazon tools and services that can help you grow your
business in Japan.
Language support is essential for selling internationally, and we provide expert support throughout
the entire selling process in Japan.
From account registration to listing and shipping, you can get support via telephone, chat, and
email.
With a professional seller, you get the convenience and efficiency of single sign-on.
After linking your accounts, you can navigate across multiple marketplaces with one username and
password.
You can see all of your accounts within the same region or across different regions with the marketplace
switcher.
To learn more about single sign-on, check out the single sign-on video in Seller University.
After linking your accounts, you can also use the Build International Listings tool, known as BIL,
to manage your product listings in Japan.
With BIL, you can add your offers and automatically synchronize the offer prices from, for example,
Amazon.
com to Amazon Japan based on the price rules you set up.
To learn more about how to set up a BIL connection, watch the "Introduction to Build International
Listings" video in Seller University.
As with all Amazon marketplaces, product listings must be in the local language.
To help you quickly list products in Japan and save on translation costs, millions of product detail
pages in various categories have already been translated from English to Japanese.
If the product you would like to sell is not currently listed on the Japan marketplace, go to Amazon.
com/SPN.
Here, you can find third-party companies on Amazon Solution Provider Network to help you with translations.
Customers in Japan expect same day or next-day delivery, and using FBA is the best way to satisfy
this demand and compete successfully in Japan.
FBA provides customer service on your behalf in Japanese so you can focus on growing your business
while we handle your customers' questions and returns.
When selling in any country, it's important to understand and comply with the local laws and regulations.
Japan has regulations on many different product categories, mostly for certain grocery, health and
personal care, electronics, and food-related products.
Japan also has special requirements regarding who can import products into the country.
Amazon knows the territory and can help you learn from our experience in the third-largest economy
in the world.
Amazon Global Selling Tools and Services can help you reach millions of Japanese customers quickly
and minimize the cost and complications of selling in Japan.
To help you understand cross-market listing, localization, fulfillment, tax and compliance, we've
put together a step-by-step guide.
You can access it on the Sell Globally page in Seller Central.
We hope to see you selling on Amazon Japan soon.
To get started, click Sell Globally below.